partnering with palo it has brought us
tremendous value they've got us to focus
on
being agile aside from just doing agile
[Music]
manulife provides superior insurance
retirement and wealth management
solutions to our customers and we've
done so for over 133 years
our bold ambition is to be the most
digital customer centric organization in
our industry
and this is really in support of our
customers and our employees
as we strive to make every day better
the need for transformational change has
never been clearer
in order for us to achieve our ambitions
agility
has to move from a mere buzzword to
being an absolute necessity
my experience with palo alt so when we
work with agile coaches
they're part of our family they work
with us as a
team during trainings also it's more of
a
experience sharing in manulife we have
an intensive and effective training
program called
kickstarter we teach our engineers good
engineering disciplines like test driven
development
behavior driven development and pair
programming
all these events are facilitated by
palo iit with their help today we have a
better understanding in agile world
and it really changed the way we work
today daily we have
two meetings in the morning meetings
team gather and discuss
about their tasks for the day and then
end of the day with our
po to demo what we have done this really
helps us to get the fast feedback from
the po
and also it's help us to make sure we
are on track
i could clearly see a cultural shift
into i.t
during our agile transformation journey
i could say so
because when new processes and behaviors
become part of existing community
there is a sign of a change a cultural
change
and this is visible in our recent
employee engagement survey
the first and immediate benefit which
achieved was
transparency and this transparency
resulted into a tremendous
trust into business teams personally i
really love
working with follow it because of the
relationship we have with palo it
coaches one thing i really like about
them is that you will not
get any textbook answers for every
situation or issue we are trying to
solve
they will always try to understand them
before they bring us
any suggestions or ideas
it's been a very exciting journey and i
look forward to continuing this
transformation journey with paolo it
[Music]